<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Screen Rotation Lock</string>
    <string name="thanks">Thank you for using the app.</string>
    <string name="thanks_first">Thank you for using the app. Please read Help for more information. If you experience any problems,
        please drop me an email so I can help you out. I usually send my replies within 24 hours.
    </string>
    <string name="thanks_old">Thank you for having been using the app. I hope it is helpful for you. If it is, please give it some
        stars on Google Play. If you experience any problems, please drop me an email with some details. Usually, I\'ll send my replies within 24 hours.
        \n\nNew feature: Introducing Quick mode. Immediately lock screen orientation to 90 degree angle when the app launch. No waiting.
    </string>
    <string name="about">The app is developed by YUH APPS. If you find any problems, please feel free to drop me an email so I can help you out or solve it
        in the next release.
    </string>
    <string name="okay">Okay</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="request_permission">
        <![CDATA[
        <p style=\"text-align:justify\">
        <b>In order to work</b> you must grant <b>WRITE SETTINGS</b> permission to the app.<br><br>
        Click the <b>button</b> below to open Settings app.
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="device_not_supported">Seems like your device is not supported</string>
    <string name="quick_help">
        <![CDATA[
        <p style="text-align:justify">
        <b>1. Rotate</b> the device screen to the orientation you want.<br><br>
        <b>2.</b> Hit the <b>Floating button</b> below to lock your screen orientation.<br><br>
        <b>3.</b> Hit the <b>Floating button</b> again to unlock your screen orientation.<br><br>
        <b>3.</b> You can enable <b>Quick mode</b> for instant orientation lock.<br><br>
        </p>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="view_help">Help</string>
    <string name="rotation_locked">Orientation locked</string>
    <string name="rotation_locked_long">Screen orientation is locked</string>
    <string name="rotation_unlocked">Orientation unlocked</string>
    <string name="rotation_unlocked_long">Screen orientation is unlocked</string>
    <string name="your_device_is_not_supported">It looks like your device is not supported.</string>
    <string name="yuhapps_on_gplay">About application</string>
    <string name="activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="help_welcome">Thank you for downloading and using the Orientation Lock. Here is the Help section.</string>
    <string name="app_purpose">The app targets Android handsets. On many of them, the you can either leave your screen orientation unlocked,
        or lock it to the portrait mode (0 degree). That may cause some inconvenience if you are watching some videos on YouTube or browsers and you
        want to lock the screen orientation to landscape in order to keep the video full screen.
        \n\nThe app is made for that purpose. By using the app, you can lock your device screen orientation to landscape mode to enjoy full screen videos,
        images or using some other apps without interruption. You can also use the app to lock your screen orientation to portrait mode as well.
        \n\nThe app has no effect on apps and games that specifically request fixed orientation, for example: homescreen launchers, Hay Day, Asphalt 8.
        Please don\'t blame and ask me to find a way to interrupt these apps and games.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_use_title">How to use the app?</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_content">You\'ll need to open the app, rotate your screen to the orientation you need (mostly landscape), then hit the floating
        button to lock the orientation, then go back to your app or home screen to launch the other app you want to launch. Please note that if your launcher
        explicitly requests portrait orientation then the screen will rotate back to portrait mode. After you open the other app, the screen will go right
        back to the landscape/portrait mode you expect.
    </string>
    <string name="no_homescreen_widget_title">Why isn\'t there a homescreen widget?</string>
    <string name="no_homescreen_widget_content">I have tried implemented the feature and yes, it works some how. However, here are some drawbacks that make
        me decide to stop working on it:
        \n\n- It requires your homescreen launcher does not have fixed orientation, in the other word, the launcher must support both portrait and landscape
        modes, which most of default launchers, both by device manufacturers and some on Play Store, don\'t.
        \n\n- It requires a background service running all the time, so that will negatively affect battery life.
        \n\n- It lags on many devices, especially on low-end ones.
        \n\nNOW YOU HAVE QUICK MODE TO QUICKLY LOCK YOUR SCREEN ORIENTATION TO LANDSCAPE_90. Please hit Quick mode from the previous Activity for more details.
    </string>
    <string name="no_qs_tile_interruption_title">Why doesn\'t the app change the default Quick Settings Tile?</string>
    <string name="no_qs_tile_interruption_content">Yes, there are some apps that change the behaviour of the default QS Tile, but I don\'t do so because
        that may cause some trouble to your device configuration. Most importantly, they won\'t undo any changes they make to your device system. My app
        does not. In case you don\'t like SOL, you can simply remove it and there would be no problem with your device system.
    </string>
    <string name="wrong_uses_title">Once you have the app installed, please don\'t use it wrong.</string>
    <string name="wrong_uses_content">
        - It doesn\'t change the behaviour of the default QS Tile: As I said above, it does not. Some brainless users, I don\'t know why, think that once
        the app is installed then they can lock the screen orientation to landscape mode BY THE BUILT-IN QS Tile. NO. You\'ll need to use the app.
        \n\n- It doesn\'t mess the soft keys: That depends on your customised Android variant by your manufacturer and that\'s their problem, not mine. If
        this app messes your keys, other similar apps on Play Store also do the same.
    </string>
    <string name="known_issues_title">Known issues</string>
    <string name="known_issues_content">The floating button lags on KitKat and earlier Android versions (Android 4.X) in landscape mode: That\'s the problem
        of FloatingActionButton class on Android 4.X. I tried a lot to fix it but I can\'t. Unless Google releases a new version of the class, I can do nothing.
    </string>
    <string name="saved">Setting is saved</string>
    <string name="change_angle">Change angle</string>
    <string name="quick_mode">Quick mode</string>
    <string name="quick_mode_message">
        <![CDATA[
        Immediately lock screen orientation to <b>%s</b> angle when you open the app. No waiting. To take advantage of the feature,
        please add the app to Home screen.<br><br>
        At the moment, the feature is <b>%s</b>.<br><br>
        Click outside of this dialog to close it without changing the current setting.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="quick_mode_is_enabled">Quick mode has been enabled</string>
    <string name="quick_mode_is_disabled">Quick mode has been disabled</string>
    <string name="enable">Enable</string>
    <string name="disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="enabled"><b>ENABLED</b></string>
    <string name="disabled"><b>DISABLED</b></string>
    <string name="quick_mode_toast">Screen orientation has been set to %s. Please launch any app for the change to take effect.
        To unlock orientation, just open the app, or hit the system QS Tile.
    </string>
    <string name="quick_unlock_title">Unlock orientation or launch the app?</string>
    <string name="quick_unlock_message">Do you want to unlock screen orientation or launch the app? Click outside of this dialog to cancel.</string>
    <string name="quick_unlock_unlock_button">Unlock screen orientation</string>
    <string name="quick_unlock_launch_app_button">Launch app</string>
    <string-array name="quick_unlock_options">
        <item>Unlock screen orientation</item>
        <item>Launch app interface</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="quick_mode_options">
        <item>Portrait_0</item>
        <item>Landscape_90</item>
        <item>Portrait_180</item>
        <item>Landscape_270</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
