<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="quick_help">
        <b>1. Rotate</b> the device screen to the orientation you want.
        \n\n<b>2.</b> Hit the <b>Floating button</b> below to lock your screen orientation.
        \n\n<b>3.</b> Hit the <b>Floating button</b> again to unlock your screen orientation.
        \n\n<b>4.</b> On Nougat and Oreo, you have a QS tile for quick access.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_use_content">You\'ll need to open the app, rotate your screen to the orientation you need (mostly landscape), then hit the floating
        button to lock the orientation, then go back to your app or home screen to launch the other app you want to launch. Please note that if your launcher
        requests portrait orientation then the screen will rotate back to portrait mode. After you open the other app, the screen will go right back to the
        landscape/portrait mode you expect.

        \nOn Android 7 Nougat and later, you also have a QuickSetting Tile that acts similar the built-in Tile. However, my QS Tile can lock the device
        orientation to the current one. For example, the screen is in landscape mode, you pull down the QS panel, hit my QS Tile and the orientation will
        be locked to landscape. So you don\'t have to open the app to perform orientation lock.
    </string>
    <string name="nougat_qs_tile_warning_title">Please remove and re-add the Tile</string>
    <string name="nougat_qs_tile_warning_message">Please remove and re-add the Tile. The app might crash. But it will work normally after the Tile is re-added.
        \n\nBecause you are on Nougat, so Quick mode is not recommended. Either you use the Tile or Quick mode. Using them both may cause the Tile not updating
        state correctly.
        \n\nAnd please remove SRL from Doze (and Samsung Battery Saving) list(s). The app is completely based on Android\'s APIs, so it does not eat any extra
        energy than the default QS Tile of Android.
    </string>
    <string name="tile_has_problem">There\'s a problem with the QS Tile. Please remove and re-add it.</string>
    <string name="please_unlock_device">Please unlock your device</string>
    <string name="auto_rotate">Auto-rotate</string>
    <string name="hide_or_show_app_icon">Hide or show app icon</string>
    <string name="hide_app_icon">Hide app icon</string>
    <string name="show_app_icon">Show app icon</string>
    <string name="app_icon_is_shown_in_launcher">App icon is now shown in launcher.</string>
    <string name="app_icon_is_hidden_in_launcher">App icon is now hidden in launcher. To enable it, long press on the QS Tile.</string>
</resources>